

# **KAMORUDEEN NURUDEEN**Web Designer

## **My Contact**

kamorudeenalowonle@gmail.com

+234-81-466-231-55

Ikeja, Lagos State, Nigeria

www.technophilesacademy.com/kan

# Hard Skill

- Web Design
- Web Development
- LAN & WAN Network Engineering
- Computer Hardware Engineering
- · Working With Microsoft Office Suite
- Agency Banking (Mobile Agent)

#### **Soft Skill**

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- Hubspot Academy
  Branding and Marketing
  Completed in 2022
- Nova University
  Certificate in Web Design Consultancy
  Completed in 2022
- All-Right Technologies
  Diploma in Desktop Publishing, Computer
  Engineering and Networking.
  Completed in 2017

#### **About Me**

I'm a Nigerian based Web Designer and Digital Marketer focused on crafting clean, user-friendly experiences and marketing strategies for small and medium enterprises.

I am passionate about building excellent websites, apps, software and online strategies that improves the lives of individuals and businesses around me.

#### **Professional Experience**

FatRuq Digital Concepts | Digittal Marketing Trainer 2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

 Training of student of the academy on Social Media Marketing and Advertising.

Haryorks Affordable Store | Online Marketer 2020 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Branding
- Web Design
- · Digital advertising
- Marketing strategies

Success Foundation School | Teacher & Head Teacher 2014 – 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Supervision of other staffs activities
- · Collection and collation of data.
- Give report to the Principal and attend to parents.

#### **Achievements**

2015 - 2017 Best Teaching Staff

2015 - 2017 Best Mathematics Teacher